By the end of summer,
到了夏末，
people seemed to lose interest.
人們似乎逐漸失去了興趣
Everyone had been holding their breath
在他們停止討論了以後，
once they stopped talking.
每個人似乎都沉默了下來
But you can only hold it for so long I suppose.
但我想有一天總會憋不住的
People have their own problems...
每個人都有自己要對付的心魔，
Even here.
無論在哪。
No more speculations...
不再猜測 、
No more tears
不再有眼淚、
or neighbourhood search parties...
也不再有鄰居組成的尋人小組。
Girls like her seem to come from somewhere else...
像她這樣的女孩，感覺完全不屬於這裡
The way she moved. .
她的一舉一動...
Like an alien...
就好像...
Living in that pool.
一個住在那座游泳池裡的外星人…
Georgina.
Her parents turned her room upside down.
她父母徹底翻遍了她的房間
But all they found was a diary
但他們唯一能找到的只有一本日記
containing daily lists of the food she ate,
持續記錄著她吃過的東西
and how far she'd swam.
和她游了多遠
Or so I heard.
至少那是我聽說的
When you don't know,
當你無法理解的時候，
truth is just what you decide it is.
你決定相信的事情就成為所謂的真相
And she never came back to tell us otherwise.
而她再也沒有回來以給我們別的解釋
She couldn't speak English at all yeah.
畢竟她根本不會說英語
The only thing she could say was
她唯一會說的一句話就是
"I love you"
[我愛你]
So basically yeah,
所以我想可以說
I fucking turned her around...
我把她迷的團團轉...
Johnny went to Thailand for two weeks.
強尼去了泰國兩個禮拜
He met a girl.
他遇見了一個女孩
They danced to techno on the beach
他們每晚都隨著電音在沙灘上跳舞
and fucked every night.
然後瘋狂做愛
He can last 45 minutes now.
他現在可以撐45分鐘
A half in football lasts 45 minutes.
那根本是半場足球的時間了
You know what I mean!
你懂的！
He don't, he's a virgin in he?
他不會懂 他還是小處男吧
How about then... How about...
那不然...不然..
Let's say... Barbara Windsor...
假設是HOLD住姊好了
Fuckin' look at that !
幹！你看那個！
Come on man, come on !
快過來！快過來！
Where'd you get that from ? !
你怎麼有這個！？
Give us a go !
讓我們玩!
Sorry, what ?
抱歉，你剛說什麼？
You might want to put a hat on !
你要不要戴頂帽子阿!
Thank you Mrs. Woods.
謝謝你，伍茲太太
Some of the guys say
有些男生會說
you have to ignore girls you like.
你要假裝無視你喜歡的女生
I can't.
我沒辦法
It's like a car crash,
這就像一次撞車，
or a drunk shouting in the street.
或是一個醉鬼在街上大喊
You just can't look away.
你不可能假裝沒看到的
I want to. .
我很想...
But I can't.
但我做不到
What ?
什麼？
Hey.
嘿
You hangover ?
你宿醉唷？
Let the boy eat his breakfast.
你讓他好好吃早餐啦
Weren't you gonna save me ?
你沒有要救我嘛？
I knew you were playing.
我知道你是裝的
It's like living with dead people in this house anyway.
反正住在這裡我就像跟死人住在一起差不多
They seem all right.
他們看起來還ok阿
Are yours happy ?
你的呢？他們快樂嘛？
I think so.
我猜是吧
Dunno.
不知道..
Well... Do they have sex after they fight ?
嗯… 他們吵玩架以後會做愛嘛？
Uh, forget about it.
痾…當我沒說好了...
If they do I just take my hearing aid out.
如果他們真的有，我會把助聽器拿掉
What's it like without that thing?
把這個拿掉會是什麼感覺阿？
Like... Like being underwater... Sort of.
就像...嗯...有點像在水底下吧...
I read that you have
我聽說如果
a better chance of sleeping with a girl
你找個藉口離開現場一下，
if you find an excuse to leave the room...
你可能會更有機會跟那個女生發生關係
So she can undress alone.
因為她可以有獨自一人的時間脫衣服
It's the undressing bit that's uncomfortable
脫衣服跟慢慢變的赤裸
about getting naked.
是不同的感覺
That's why doctors pull a curtain.
這也是為什麼在醫院你會有布簾擋著
One. .
一...
. . Two. .
二...
. . Three. .
三...
At the bottom, she wanted to tell me a secret
在水底的時候 她想用
in exchange for one of mine.
一個祕密交換我的一個祕密
Only had the one.
只有一個
I don't even think it was a secret.
我甚至不覺得那是秘密
Mrs. Phillips came by the house.
菲利浦太太來過一趟，
Said you promised to do her rose-bushes
他說你沒有依約整理他們的玫瑰花
You should keep your promises.
你應該遵守承諾的
Hey... How you doing ?
嘿... 你還好嘛？
Hello !
哈囉！
What's his name then Clare ?
Clare, 你說他叫什麼名字?
Oh come on !
幹嘛這樣!
I told you. You've forgotten.
我上次有說阿! 你忘了，
I'm not telling you again.
我沒有要再告訴你一次唷
Does she has a man ?
她有男人？
She hasn't got one. She's never.
.應該還沒，她從來
- She's never had one. - Right
- 她沒交過男朋友  -對啦對啦
- I just wanna say… - Speech !
- 我只是想說... - 開講囉！！
It's not a speech. It just wanna say...
沒那麼誇張，我只是想講講
...That family is important. And...
我想說家庭真的很重要, 然後...
to be able to get to your twenty year anniversary
可以組成一個家庭度過二十個年頭...
Eighteen hon.
是十八，親愛的
Whatever. . It's not nothing.
總之，這真的不容易
And... Well I just don't know how you do it.
然後... 我真的不知道你們怎麼辦到的！
Thank you Clare, that's very nice.
謝謝你Clare， 你真好
To the family.
敬家庭！
Family.
敬家庭
Are they under the table?
有沒有在桌子底下阿？
-No. - Look under the table.
-沒阿！ - 看一下桌子下面
Ah, what colour are they ?
那他們是什麼顏色的呢？
Well they're brown - like the carpet !
是咖啡色，剛好跟地毯一樣！
Maybe you came without the shoes.
你是不是根本沒有穿鞋子來阿？
I didn't come without shoes !
我有穿鞋子來好嘛！
- Is this them ? - No!
- 是這雙嘛？ - 不是！
Oh there they are !
喔喔在這邊！！
Let's get you a cab.
我們幫你叫車吧！
You start loading. I'll get the rest.
你先開始清，我等一下會來幫你
Take these up, okay?
把這拿上樓好嗎？
- Hi. - Hi.
- 哈囉 - 嗨
Hi. What are you doing here ?
哈囉，請問你有什麼事嗎？
Just visiting Sam, the door was open...
我只是來看看Sam, 你們門是開的...
- Hi. - Hi.
- 嗨  - 嗨
I'm sorry.
剛剛對不起
Wouldn't it be funny if they thought
如果他們以為我們在那個，
that we were doing it?
應該會很好笑吧？
Uh, come on Sam, don't look so serious.
ㄟ 你不要看起來這麼嚴肅嘛
I auditioned for a school play once,
我曾經去學校的
only for a small part.
一個短劇試鏡
The director said I wasn't convincing.
導演說我聽起來沒有說服力
I have to go.
我該走了
She gave the part to someone else.
她最後把那個角色給別人了
Um... Could you walk me out ?
嗯... 你可以陪我走出去嘛？
What time?
什麼叫他長大了？
You don't know what you are talking about...
你根本不知道你在說什麼！
Congratulations Georgina. Well done.
恭喜呀 Georgina, 拿獎牌耶！
Say it to the girl who won.
去跟那個得到的女孩說吧
You've disrespected the family
你並沒有尊重這個家庭，
and upset your mum.
還讓你的母親很傷心
We... We were just...
我們... 我們只是...
Do you understand, Samuel ?
你了解嘛？Samuel
Yes.
我了解了
There's lemonade inside.
裡面有飲料唷！
I think I should maybe finish. .
我想先撈完這些...
... Finish the leaves...
葉子...
Cheers.
快喝吧
The garden looks wonderful Sam.
我們的花園變得好漂亮，Sam
Thank you.
謝謝你
Yeah.
對..
I'd better go and finish the pool.
我最好去把游泳池清完
Maybe she was showing Dad
也許她表演給我爸看
what we were doing the other day.
我們那天在做什麼
But it didn't sound like a joke anymore.
但這次聽起來是玩真的了
Maybe Dad joined in.
也許我爸加入了...
Found it funny.
也許為了好玩
Maybe he told her I was a virgin.
也許她告訴我爸我是處男
They probably laughed about it.
也許他們一起嘲笑我
I bet he made her come.
我敢保證他讓她高潮了
Maybe they smoked cigarettes afterwards.
也許他們還會抽事後煙
They do in films.
像電影一樣
Except in porn.
除了A片
Porn just ends.
A片會直接結束
My baby boy.
我的小寶貝
Growing up so fast.
你長大得好快
Girls don't just disappear.
女生不會就突然消失
What if he strangled her to death
會不會是他有一次在玩
in one of those sex games.
他們的性遊戲的時候把她勒死了
You all right ?
你還好嘛？
Maybe when Geogina's dad came by that night...
也許當Geogina的爸爸來按門鈴的那晚
... Dad lied.
我爸撒謊了...
Maybe Mum knew.
也許老媽什麼都知道
What did you do Dad ?
爸，你做了什麼？
What's wrong with you ?
你到底有什麼毛病！
Or maybe I just imagined the noise.
也許那些聲音都是我想像出來的
Maybe Georgina ran away...
也許Georgina只是逃走了
Got tired of her parents
厭倦了她的父母、
and swimming and school and all that.
游泳、學校和一切
She could be on a beautiful beach somewhere.
她可能正在某處一座美麗的沙灘上
Eating with her hands...
用手吃著東西
Dancing around the fire...
圍著營火跳舞..
and skinny-dipping in the ocean.
在大海裡裸泳...
Maybe she's in love with a guy
也許她愛上了一個可以撐
who can last 45 minutes.
四十五分鐘的男人
45 minutes. .
四 -- 十 -- 五分鐘....
That sounds like a long time.
聽起來超久的...